Now everybody lift your hands up!
Sing about what you are dreaming!
Always stand up!
Raise up the flag that can't be beaten!
Gotta keep up!
We'll get past every wall that's
in our wake, go without hesitation!
Hands up!
We just have to press on a little more.
To get to the answers we're looking for.
We came to this new world believing.
That surely someday we
just might find the way.
All the pieces of our dreams
have now come together.
Our bonds won't waver.
With our dreaming hand.
Let's head on towards.
A bright new future.
Now everybody lift your hands up.
Sing about what you are dreaming.
Always stand up.
Raise up the flag that you believe in.
Gotta keep up.
We'll get past everyone that's in our way.
Let's head on never stopping.
Only look up.
Keep your head up way up high.
Always step up.
If waves are rough, jump to the sky.
Never give up.
Our wishes, they will come together.
And lead us on for the future.
We drift on riding the waves.
Towards another shore day by day.
There are many meetings, many goodbyes.
Underneath the flag we fly.
I'll remember the pain within.
I'll keep it in my heart forever.
And never take it lightly.
But I won't surrender.
This freedom I will keep in mind.
I'll keep holding on, never stop it.
Now everybody lift your hands up.
Sing about what you are dreaming.
Always stand up.
Raise up the flag that you believe in.
Gotta keep up.
We'll get past everyone that's in our way.
Let's head on, never stop it.
Only look up, keep your
head up way up high.
Always step up, if brains
are rough, jump to the sky.
Never give up, our wishes,
they will come together.
And lead us on for the future.
Hands up.
All right, G5, let's step on it!
Captain Tashigi needs us
to save those children!
I guess Caesar's not the
only Logia type here.
I don't know about that, but either
way, she's out of our league.
Hey, Blackleg, while we're on the subject,
why didn't you help when you
started trying to kill us?
You're stronger than
all of us put together.
Get over it.
I won't kick a woman no
matter how evil she is. Huh?
Are you kidding me?
But what if it came down to
a matter of life and death?
I choose death. What?
No way.
They're all in the same crew, but
they're so different from each other.
Yeah, just look at that
pirate hunter's orb.
He seemed like the type
of person who would
chop you to bits if you
even looked at him funny.
Well, he's got a sensitive side, too.
Don't worry about him, though.
He'll find a way out.
And the same thing goes for Tashigi.
All that matters now is tracking
down that group of rugrats so Nami,
Robin, and Tashigi will tell
us we did a good job! Yeah!
Go with your soldiers.
I'll do as I please.
I said I don't need your help.
They're entitled to your opinion.
Oh, really?
If that's how you feel, then am I entitled
to cut you up first, Miss Navy Captain?
I am a pirate.
No, you can't. Huh?
You won't put a scratch on me.
Or her, for that matter.
You think so, huh?
Well, what do you know?
I was just thinking the same thing.
Am I wrong?
you're letting me live
it's because i'm a girl
jeez woman do you ever
shut your damn mouth
listen you get the same exact
face as some chick i knew who
died so i can't stand the sight
of you on top of that i don't
know a thing about you yet and
you're already talking just
like her why the hell are you
copying her just try to be herself
maybe you ought to think before you talk
you think that women aren't as strong you
hold back in a fight so
you can't kill her can
you you're never gonna
succeed that way that's
why i stayed because
you're not up to the task
with the powers that she's got if she
gets near my men i know it won't be pretty
are you trying to say
you're better than me yes
I've had it then
I'm supposed to keep her
claws off my comrades too,
you know As long as someone keeps
her busy, what's the difference?
You shouldn't be so flippant.
Look, we don't have much time.
You'd better run while you still can.
Stay focused.
One bite and you're dead meat.
He's right.
And thanks to you, I've just
discovered his weakness.
You may have your Haki, but that
won't be enough to save you from me!
Cute trick!
You can use Haki to force a power
user like me back to my normal state.
That said, you have to be fast
enough to catch up with me!
Sorry, dear.
You're colder than I thought.
Oh, I'm cold?
You're the snow woman.
Don't you ignore me!
Care for a snowball fight?
Snow rabbit!
Perhaps I underestimated you.
You are Smoker's right-hand girl.
Oh, great!
Once I end you,
I'll go find your troops and say, your
poor captain just couldn't cut it.
It's my shoulder!
She bit it off!
Let go of me!
Damn you!
If I let go, I'll lose my shoulder.
I gave you a chance, but if
you'd rather, I tear you apart.
If you hadn't been running your
mouth, you'd be done with her by now.
But your time's up.
I'm busy, so let's make
this quick, all right?
I could have sworn he wouldn't cut a
woman, but it looks like I was wrong.
He swung at me without
a moment's hesitation.
So you've misjudged me.
How about that?
That was a fatal mistake.
Maybe I don't go around
cutting just anyone, but still.
Well, think.
When you're face to face with an
animal that can rip you to shreds,
you don't take any chances, do you?
You get the hell out of there.
Oh, well. Too late.
What's happening to me?
I can't move my feet.
One sword style.
He'll kill me.
Great dragon shock.
All right, we're done here. It's over.
He got her.
How...
how dare you!
Did she not die?
That's odd.
He didn't use his haki.
She lost control of her body.
She must have been
petrified when she realized
that she'd die if Zoro used his Haki.
I've never seen anything like that.
I wonder what the Straw Hat Pirates were
doing during those two
years they went missing.
How much stronger are they now?
It's amazing.
You're not getting away now!
Autumn rain!
Sorry, bud.
You're finished.
What was all that about?
After everything you said, you
still didn't try to kill that girl.
See?
I was right about you.
And you can't deny it.
I don't recall asking you to
finish my fight for me, Captain.
If you hadn't killed her, I would have.
You just stepped in.
Hey, that's not fair.
You can't say that.
I stepped in because you were leaving.
Nobody forced you.
But hey.
Good job, Miss Four Eyes.
She's dead, so she can't
hurt anyone else anymore.
I don't mind if you take the credit.
Could you be more patronizing?
You think you're better than me?
Pretty much.
We have to go!
Yeah, come on.
Hey, what are you doing, raccoon?
Get off of me!
It's a sedative.
This will help you.
Hey, what happened to me? Candy!
Quick, go after the children! Right.
Get back here with our kitty, Mocha!
Come back!
Milky Hall!
This again?
We won't be able to keep this up long.
How much further does Mocha have to go?
Where to now?
This place is huge!
I don't know which way to go anymore!
The toxic gas is flowing
into the biscuit room.
What's the problem?
The exit's in the other direction.
What?
You could have told me sooner.
Will you at least put me down
before we catch up with my men?
Swallow your pride for once.
It's not like it'll do you
any good if you're dead.
Jeez, what now?
I don't believe it.
Is that the legendary sword shoestring?
Give your hands to yourself and stop
running your mouth, you stupid sword geek.
No!
Mocha?
Ew!
Please stop this! Mocha! Oh, no!
Some of them took another route!
Please! Mocha! Mocha! Mocha!
If they get the candy, we'll
have to start all over again!
We have to get Mocha away from them!
I just want to get away from this
stupid island and go back home!
She ate all of it!
That's not fair! Mocha!
What was she thinking?
No, Gabby!
Can't just look at all! Gabby!
No, ma!
Mocha!
You need to spit them all out right now!
Do you hear me? Mocha!
I told you what those candies really are!
I'm sorry, Chopper.
I had to do it!
They're my friends!
It's not too late!
You can still spit them out!
I promise!
You know what I think we
should do when we grow up?
We should find a ship and
set out for the open sea!
The sea?
Why, to catch fish?
No, dummy, to go on an adventure.
You know, look for islands made
of gold and stuff like that.
That sounds like fun.
When we get better and go home,
we'll be separated, right?
We won't see each other anymore.
That's why we need a
ship, to pick everyone up.
Yeah, cool, let's go.
A bunch of friends having a big adventure.
So, what's the plan?
When do we go?
Let's see.
I don't know when we're 20 years old.
That's like forever from now—waiting for
so long will just make it more exciting!
Yeah,
okay, let's make it a promise.
So
the master is a bad person, yes?
A very bad person!
person But he's always been
so nice to us the candy.
He gives us is yummy and
we get to eat it every day
That's how he trapped you What? But why?
You children aren't...
his test subjects. How...
how do you know? Hey, Mocha!
Open up!
We need to go to the
biscuit room right now!
Candy!
The truth is, none of you were
sick when he brought you here.
That can't be true!
You're wrong!
How do you think you wound
up with a body that enormous?
I've heard rumors about experiments that
have been going on for
hundreds of years now.
People all around the world
attempting to create giants.
I say attempting because nobody
has ever succeeded before.
The experiments always fail.
I'm sorry, but there's something
that I have to tell you.
Caesar's experiment is doomed too.
He knows that it's going to fail.
My guess is he's just collecting
data for his next experiment.
So, what's going to happen to us?
Death.
None of you will live to see home again.
That delicious candy is a fatal toxin.
It tastes sweet, but the truth
is, it's destroying your body.
And as soon as you eat one,
you start to crave another.
The more you eat, the more
control Caesar has over you.
Before long, you'll do
anything for another piece.
Just like those kids in there.
I sedated you.
That's why you're calm now.
But there are side effects from the
candy and the experiment itself.
Before you reach adulthood,
you will likely die.
We won't ever be grown-ups?
That can't be right.
What about our homes,
our mommies and daddies?
Will we get to see them again?
You won't, unless you leave soon.
A lot of things have scared us here.
We never even thought about that, though.
When we asked you for help, it was
because we wanted to go home again.
We wanted the chance to see
our families instead of being
stuck here another year without
knowing what we were sick with.
We never...
We never actually thought that we
were going to die here, though.
We thought we were going to
leave here once we got better.
That's what he said, and we believed him.
Um, we ate that candy
because they gave it to us!
We didn't know we would die from it!
Yes, I know!
It's not your fault, none of this is!
That's why we're gonna do whatever
it takes to defeat Caesar!
Nothing will stop us!
I'm sorry!
So sorry that we didn't get here
sooner to save you from him!
We can't die!
Please stop her.
I don't want to die here.
Then it won't happen.
We'll find a way to save you.
Caesar's strong.
He's powerful, devious, and maybe the
most horrible man in the entire world.
But you should know something.
Our captain is better
than him and stronger.
As a matter of fact, he's going
to be king of the pirates someday.
He can do it.
No matter what, Luffy is
going to take Caesar down.
So please listen carefully.
I think I have a plan.
We can't let the other
children have any more candy.
Do you understand?
I'm going to do my best to
get them all sedated here.
That should make them easier.
To control but I need your help.
Do you think you can go to the
biscuit room and guard the candies!
Yes!
Whatever I have to do, I'll make
sure nobody eats any more candy!
I want us all to escape together!
Okay.
I think she puked blood. Why though?
All she did was eat the candy.
She really doesn't look good.
I can't believe it.
The children have stopped now.
That's what happens when you're greedy.
What's wrong? See now?
This is what eating the
candy really does to you!
Do you get it?
Mocha, sacrifice yourself!
For you!
To save you!
Chopper, if you want to sedate
them, then now is your best chance.
Mocha, first I have to treat her!
No time, Chopper.
The children are standing still!
Let's go!
Yeah!
No violence, boys!
Don't hurt anybody!
Yeah!
Just subdued!
Do not injure!
Yeah!
Get them under control!
All right!
Hey, it's Sanji!
And the Navy? Sanji!
Blackleg!
He's aiming for the ball!
Balls considered violence?
Hmm.
A close call, but yes. Got it!
Medical team, you're up!
Yes, sir!
Chopper, use these guys!
They know a thing or two!
Right!
Let's get these kiddos a little calmer!
Here we go!
If I'm correct, there should be an
examination room somewhere around here!
Let's get her there as fast as we can!
We're running out of time!
You know that, right, Raccoon?
Trust me, I know!
Enough chit-chat!
Let's move! Yeah!
Chopper!
Mocha, are you okay?
Chopper, I did it!
They're safe!
I didn't let them have the candy!
You're so strong!
Eating the candy to save them!
That was brave!
It was so brave!
Thanks to you, they'll be
able to escape from here.
Mocha, I'm going to save you
no matter what I have to do.
I swear I will.
You are going to grow up.
It's Straw Hat Luffy!
What's he doing here?
Where's Caesar?
Go straight down this corridor
and building art! He's there!
Good.
I'm ready.
you